Well, if I was born in Moscow, my home
Ну если я родилась в Москве моя родная
country is Russia, if I am a person there,
страна - это Россия если я там человек
born in Chechnya, his home country is
родился в Чечне его родная страна
Chechnya Hello Hello, you are
Чечня Здравствуйте Здравствуйте Вам есть
18 years old I will not discuss politics with you
18 лет Я не буду с вами политику
I am not talking about not talking about
обсуждать У меня нет не про не про
politics I am 18 years old Yes I am  It's
политику есть 18 лет Да у меня се день
my birthday 19 Cool Cool yes
рождения меня 19 Круто Круто да
Happy birthday to you Let's
Поздравляю Вас с днём рождения Давайте
not talk about politics What are you talking about if
не про политику О чём вы говорите если
not about politics
не о политике
who really cares Well, like
кого что волнует на самом деле Ну типа
yes  interlocutors who are worried about something in
есть собеседники которых волнует что-то
their life, they ask me
их жизненное они у меня там спрашивают
something there, one guy actually asked
что-то там один мужик вообще спрашивал
said I’m not happy with my wife, she
говорил меня не устраивает моя жена она
doesn’t give it to me And you, like, and you
мне не даёт А и вы типа и вы мужикам
help men, like what you gave Yes, that’s what I
помогаете типа что давали Да вот этого я
just listened to all of him  you
просто слушала все его проблемы вы
listened to the problems And you are a psychologist Yes, you are studying to become a
слушала А Вы психолог Да вы учитесь на
psychologist No, I don’t understand Well, let’s see
психолога Нет не я понял Ну давайте вот
what we’ll talk about with
О чём о чём мы поговорим с
you. They give me everything fine, so I
вами Мне дают мне всё нормально поэтому
won’t complain, let
жаловаться не буду давайте
you stream Yes, I stream, you can
вы вы стрими Да стримлю вот можете
tell me on YouTube  I'm subscribed to everyone,
ютубчик сказать Я на всех подписано
Ukrainian, almost everyone,
украинских почти всех
drop everything in the chat, I'll
все скиньте в чат я так
take a look, my favorite is this Well, one
посмотрю мой самый любимый это Ну один
of my favorites is Eastern Prometheus
из любимых это Восточный Прометей
Eastern Prometheus, he's got a mustache, yeah,
Восточный Прометей это усатенький да да
you like that mustache, yeah, his mustache is
этот вам усы нравятся Да его его усы это
just something I don't know, I got it, I got it,
просто нечто Я не знаю Всё понял понял
in short, his mustache  like I won’t talk about it
короче усы типа это не буду говорить по
with Well, I know, I understand, well, in short, my
с Ну я знаю я поняла ну короче ещё самый
favorite one is just One love, which I
любимый - это просто One love которого я
watch constantly, every Stream of his, this is
смотрю постоянно каждый его Стрим это
less Stream, we have already
меньше Стрим мы с ним не раз уже
met more than once Who  who are mi inshi Stream And we are inshi
виделись Кто кто ми инши Стрим А мы инши
streams Yes I know I know these guys are
стримы Да знаю знаю этих пацанов
beautiful beautiful at least Well like I have a
прекрасные прекрасные хоть Ну типа я у
flag hanging there he also has a
меня флаг висит там у него тоже
Ukrainian flag you have a flag hanging yes yes And
украинский флаг у вас флаг висит да да И
you are not talking about politics yes Well
вы не о политике разговариваете да Ну
today I don’t want to I have today Well  you sing
сегодня не хочу У меня сегодня Ну поете
when I talk about politics it
когда я разговариваю о политике у меня
spoils my mood the meaning is today on this
портится настроение смысл сегодня в этот
day it spoils my mood and it’s your
день мне портит настроение а у вас День
birthday Yes yes yes I said wait and
рождения Да да да я же сказала подожди а
you support a special operation yes I
Вы спецоперацию поддерживаете да Мне в
basically understand I’m very  twofold
принципе понимаете У меня очень двоякая
Well, like, I don’t listen to the news, every day they
Ну типа я не слушаю новости каждый день
throw in something new. I just ask. Will
вбрасывает что-то новое Я просто спроси
you support the special operation, yes or no? I
Вы поддержите спецоперацию да или нет Я
support Well, in principle, yes, because
поддерживаю Ну в принципе да потому что
this is my country. But I’m ambivalent about this; in
это моя страна Но к этому отношусь я
fact, since it’s your
двояко на самом де раз у вас День
birthday, that means  I have a great
рождения Значит у меня есть прекрасный
chance to spoil the mood of a person
шанс испортить настроение человеку
who supports a special operation on his
который поддерживает спецоперацию в его
birthday. Well, I’m telling you this purely
рождения Ну это я вам это чисто потому
because it’s my country, but you didn’t listen to the end, I didn’t
что моя страна но вы не дослушали не
listen to the end, I’m ambivalent about this
дослушали я отношусь к этому двояко
Because there is  huge mistakes and punctures and
Потому что есть огромен ошибки проколы и
I see from our side that we are a fact,
я вижу с нашей стороны что мы это факт
that is, the most important mistake is that you
то есть самое главная ошибка это что вы
went to Ukraine This is the very gla this is a
попёрлись в Украину Вот это сама гла это
fact because everyone of this Well, like this is so, what do
факт потому что всем этого Ну типа это
you support then what do
так а что же вы поддерживаете тогда что
you support because this  my
вы поддерживаете потому что это моя
country Damn, I can’t, purely for
страна Блин я не могу чисто вот из
my own personal reasons, not
своего личного соображения не
support my country and not even the
поддерживать свою страну и именно даже
president, but the inhabitants, our people
не президента а жителей наш народ
who are going and even fighting against us are
который идт жи а то то воюет против нас
still fighting the people and not the president,
всё-таки воюет Народ а не президент да
yeah, well, like, in fact  yes That is, you are fighting.
да ну типа по факту да То есть вы воюете
That is, it turns out that
То есть получается значит за все
you are responsible for all the murders in Ukraine yes Well,
убийства в Украине Вы ответственны да Ну
we will be responsible in the future of course And
мы будем отвечать в дальнейшем конечно И
me and my
я и моя
mother are all these children Yes in Ukraine in
мама вот этих всех детей Да в Украине на
your hands well personally in mine no
ваших руках ну лично на моих нет потому
because I’m like No you  they just said
что я как Нет вы же только что сказали
that, hold it, not that it’s the whole
это ж подержи не то что там это всю
country, our people. Well, let it be on
страну наш народ Хорошо пусть будет на
mine, let it be on mine, yes. That is,
моих пусть будет на моих да То есть вы
today,
сегодня
uh, it’s your birthday, you were drinking
ээ у вас День рождения вы попивали
some kind of drink. Yes, blow out the cake.
какой-то там напиток Да тортик задувай
Yes, for example, or something-  then And this is not  Have you ever
Да например или что-то А в это и не
wondered how much is on these
задумывались сколько на ваших вот этих
hands of yours? Yes How much
ручках Да Сколько
blood? Well, it happens that I can do with it,
крови Ну бывает что я могу с этим
but the souls of the children of
сделать а в к вам не приходят души детей
these children who died in dreams in a dream don’t come to you, no, I didn’t
этих погибших во снах во сне не я не
call them, not like that, not that I didn’t
призывала их не так не то что не
call them, they themselves can, bye bye  I
призывала они сами могут при пока пока я
won’t call them, they won’t come They’ll come to me, they’ll
не призову они не придут Ко мне придут
come and ask for this and that and they’ll
придут и спросят такая и такие будут
scream, support
кричать поддерживаешь
the special operation like we died, just in
спецоперацию как мы умерли только в
great pain, imagine that it won’t
больших муках прикинь такое
be a big deal, expel me, don’t expel me,
будет ничего страшного изгони не изгони
don’t expel me, it’s possible  yes, look, you are a
не изгони возможно то есть смотри ты
representative of just such a cynical
представитель как раз вот такой циничной
breed, yes, you just support
породы да вы просто поддерживаете
murder because yes, this is your country.
убийство потому что да это ваша страна
Well, I’m not. And I’m very sorry. I sincerely feel
Ну я не И мне очень жалко Мне искренне
sorry for the children because I heard. Well, like,
жалко детей потому что я слышала Ну типа
I think it’s wrong, absolutely
я считаю неправильным абсолютно
wrong to kill the children of innocent
неправильным убивать детей невинных
people, not even children.  But like a man sitting
людей даже не детей Но типа сидит
at home in
дома раке
general And how did you want to see this war
вообще А как ты хотела видеть эту войну
without people dying?
без того чтобы погибали люди не хотела
Well, like my goals weren’t
видеть Ну типа моих целях не было
there once in the twenty-second year in the
когда-то там в двадцать втором году в
twenty-first Yes, but now you
двадцать первом Да но сейчас ты
support, look instead of
поддерживаешь смотри вместо того чтобы в
tell your country uh listen country
своей стране сказать ээ слушайте страна
Why should we Why should we all
А зачем мы Почему мы должны все
support this war Maybe it would be better if
поддерживать эту войну Может лучше чтобы
they took these troops back to
они забрали эти войска вернулись на
the territory of the Russian Federation we all
территорию Российской Федерации мы все
lived in peace and the Ukrainians
спокойно жили и украинцы спокойно
lived in peace Well, what’s the use of this? Well,
жили Ну а какой толк то от этого ну а
what’s the use of  here to kill And
какой толк от того чтобы тут убивать А
when How many years will you continue to
когда Сколько лет Вы ещё будете тут
kill people here, how do I know? Well,
убивать людей я откуда знаю Ну вот
look, 5 years 10 years, that’s how long it will be,
смотри 5 лет 10 лет вот сколько будет
it’s not too much of that, it’s not necessary,
это не это слишком много такого не надо
everything’s already good, that is, it’s time to
пара уже всё хорош то есть пора выходить
leave Ukraine, really, everything’s good, yes  Oh,
из Украины правда всё хорош да О то
maybe after all, yes. We shouldn’t support
может всё-таки да Надо не поддерживать
our state, but say, listen, it’s
своё государство а сказать слушайте нам
time for us to leave there, we did something a lot
пора оттуда уходить мы что-то много
bad, and every day it’s getting
плохого сделали и с каждым днём оно всё
worse and worse. Well,
хуже и хуже
I won’t do this purely
Ну я не буду этого делать чисто потому
because I don’t want to, so what’s the point?  I feel sorry for them, I feel sorry for them,
что не хочу нуну мне смысл Ну жалко их
like, what am I going to do about this? Well, I feel sorry for
жалко типа я что с этим сделаю Ну жалко
the people, I feel
людей
sorry for you, you support your mom and dad
жалко ты поддерживаешь свою маму и папу
in
во
everything, but you support the country in everything, not
всём а страну поддерживаешь во всём не
in everything, again, I didn’t say that in
во всём опять же я не говорила что во
everything I support my country, why should you?
всём я свою страну по что ж тебя
obliges you to support your country in this
обязывает поддержать свою страну в этой
war,
войне
I want one hundred my desire is precisely this,
м хоче сто мо желание именно в этом
live n then you respond that this is my
пожи п ты тогда отзываешься что это моя
country, just say I want people in
страна просто скажи Я хочу чтобы людей в
Ukraine, this is my
Украине это моё
desire Yes, I think
желание Да я считаю
that it is
что там
necessary there and who is it, give me an example oh one
надо а кто вот назви мне пример ой один
guy  whom I have already written down three times three times
мужик которого я записывала уже раз три
three of this
раза три вот этого
person. Yeah. That is, you want
человека Ага То есть вы хотите при в эту
some people from chat roulette in this.
каких-то людей с чат рулетки
Yes, this is not only chat roulette;
Да это не только чат рулетки их вне чат
you know how many of them outside chat roulette.  in Russia you are
рулетки знаете сколько А в России у вас
from what city in Russia? From what city
Из какого города Росси Из какого города
it doesn’t matter it doesn’t matter Marik Come
неважно важно не неважно Марик Приди
now I’m calling Marik I have
сейчас я вызываю Марика у меня
artificial intelligence like Marik Well
искусственный интеллект такой Марик Ну
now Find
сейчас Найди
daddy I even know what you will say
дайди Я знаю даже что вы скажете пото
because there is a special heat that
что специально есть течка такая которая
shows a certain city of which Yes
показывает определённый город котором Да
yes  In short, you can tell by the face there
да там по лицу короче можно определить
is something like that, but you have to break away, look at it
есть такое но надо оторваться так смотри
And imagine So you like
А представь Так вот ты любишь на море
to go to the sea Yes, that’s what you
ездить Да вот как ты
think when you’re at sea by a shark
думаешь когда тебя на море акула Должны
Should Ukrainians cry?  Should they
ли украинцы плакать Должны ли нейтрально
be neutral or should they laugh at
относиться или должны смеяться с
this neutrally Why
этого нейтрально Почему
SGA Neya the difference is like I’m laughing at someone
СГА Нея разница типа я что над кем-то
b Glum and I’m telling you if
смеюсь б Глум и Я те я тебе говорю если
I read in the news tomorrow that you’re
я завтра прочитал в новостях что тебя
a shark yes Or in short Kamaz there or that I’d
акула да Или короче Камаз там или что я
really laugh  Well, really, it’s
реально бы ржал ну реально это же
cool that you support
прикольно что ты которая поддерживает
special operations. Knows knows.
спецоперации Знает знает Вы тоже значит
You also support,
вы тоже поддерживаете
look again. That is, it turns out that
ещё раз смотри То есть получается что ты
you support the war against Ukraine. Yes, so there are
ты поддерживаешь войну против Украины Да
people here. Yes, but if you’re a shark
тут чтоб тут людей Да но если тебя акула
Ukrainians should have a neutral attitude towards this
украинцы должны нейтрально к этому
Yes, Ukrainians should receive
отнестись Да украинцы должны получать
incredible incredible that
неимоверное неимоверное та
satisfaction you understand Look at this
удовлетворение понимаешь Смотри это эту
T roulette shark you understand and all such oh
Т рулетки акула понимаешь и все такие о
memes think about it you have become the heroine of mmov
мемчики прикиньте вы стали героиней ммов
so this is inadequate in fact here you
така это неадекватно на самом деле вот
can question why this is this divine
можно вопрос почему это это божественное
conduct look You wanted a Ukrainian  And
проведение смотрите Вы хотели украинца А
you're a shark Well, it's just it works
вас акула Ну это Это просто это работает
purely because I've loved Ukrainians all my life
чисто потому что я всю жизнь любила
I don't like Ukrainians purely
украинцев Мне не нравятся украинцы чисто
because what they are Love because you yes That
потому какие они Люб потому что вы да То
is, you you You don’t like Ukrainians That
есть вы вы Вам не нравятся украинцы То
is, you don’t like a certain nation
есть вам не нравится определённая нация
yes yes So I don’t like Uzbeks I don’t like
да да Вот я не люблю узбеков Я не люблю
Ukrainians Here you are yes you are a classic
украинцев Вот вот вы да вы классическая
Russian yes you have a lot of Nazis very
россиян да у вас много нацистов очень
handy yes Well  listen, in your country there
кстати да Ну слушайте у вас в стране
are also people who don’t like other
есть тоже люди которые не любят другие
nationalities of American dances
национальности танцев амери
in Russia but don’t like Ukrainians, here
в России но не любите украинцев вот
Ukrainians live in Ukraine Yes, but you don’t
украинцы живут в Украине Да но вы их не
like them and you don’t like Uzbeks in
любите и узбеков не любите на тоже
There are also Ukrainians. And who are you by nationality?
украинцы есть А вы кто по национальности
Well, there is no Russian nationality,
Ну национальности русский нет
what can you call it? If you can say Slavyanka, then let it be Slavyanka, there is no
Славянка то пусть будет Славянка нет
such nationality.
такой национальности
Slavyanka, Russian. Russian, I understand, that
Славянка Россиянка Россиянка понял да то
is, in short, no
есть короче
one, well, for you, this is no one by
никто ну для вас это никто по
citizenship, Russian,
гражданству Россиянка
asking you, can I ask you a question?
попрос вам задать можно вопрос вам
ask Why depreciate in your country
задать Почему у вас в стране
When there is a war then the
обесценивай Когда идт война тогда идт
economy declines, that’s all And that is,
падение экономики вот и всё А то есть
Therefore, you need to depreciate yours again,
Поэтому нужно обесценить вашу ещё раз у
wait with you  how much is the ruble in
вас подожди у вас сколько сейчас рубль в
dollars now? Yes, the dollar, more precisely, how much the moment
долларах Да доллар точнее сколько момент
when I looked it was 82 rubles, the dollar Yes, and
когда я смотрела было 82 руб доллар Да а
a couple of years ago, how much was the dollar? No
пару лет назад сколько был доллар Без
idea, that is, uh, before uh,
понятия то есть ээ до э меньше рублей
they gave less rubles for the dollar, yes, that is, your ruble is
давали за доллар да то есть у вас рубль
depreciating, right? Why not, it’s not
обесценивается правда Почему нет не
depreciating? Why
обесценивается Почему обесценивается у
Everything depreciates in value with us. We count in rubles. I buy in
нас всё Мы считаем в рублях я покупаю в
rubles. Also, look if it’s a dollar, for example,
рубля ещё смотри если доллар да например
now they give 80 something rubles for a dollar,
сейчас за доллар дают 80 С чем-то рублей
but once they gave 50, for example, rubles.
а когда-то давали 50 например рублей Так
So you have  the currency is depreciating
то у вас обесценивается
No idea, probably not, it’s
валюта Без понятия наверное нет это
normal That the dollar is
нормально Что доллар
jumping Well, like, you know, that’s the point, that’s
скачет Ну типа смысл понимаете это смысл
not the point here in Ukraine, you keep
не в этом у вас в Украине вы всё
counting people in chat roulette, they say
считаете люди в чат-рулетке м говорят
Convert this to dollars But you know
Переведи в доллары это Но знаеш знаешь
why, it’s normal because look,
почему нормально потому что смотри для
if you  you communicate, for example, in rubles,
того если ты общаешься например в рублях
and I communicate in hryvnias in order to
а я общаюсь в гривнах для того чтобы
understand how much uh to bring to one
понять сколько ээ привести к одному
common measurement Yes, for example, for
общему измерению Да например вот ты
example, you say there in feet yes, and I say in
например говоришь там в футах да А я в
meters  we will compare Who has more
метрах как мы сравним У кого больше
less or according to we must bring it to one
меньше или по мы должны привести к одной
unit of measurement Yes, therefore, what is the
единиц измерения Да поэтому в чём
problem to ask and what is the problem
проблема спросить а в чём проблема
to ask how much it will be in hryvnias
спросить сколько это будет в гривнах
if a person Well, like, he comes in because
если человеку Ну типа он зайти потому
yes, look, I’ll explain why in both ways
что да смотри по обя объясняю почему
Because, for example, a person in  In Ukraine,
Потому что например человек в Украине
he rarely operates in rubles; in
так он редко оперирует рублями человек в
Russia, he rarely operates in hryvnias; more
России редко оперирует гривнами так
precisely, in Ukraine he often
точнее так долларом в Украине чаще
operates with dollars than with rubles; in Russia, he
оперирует чем рублями долларом в России
operates with dollars more often than with hryvnias; therefore, it is
чаще оперирует чем гривнами поэтому
logical that we should take some equivalent
логично что взять какой-то эквивалент
to which  it’s easier for everyone to come to the dollar Yes, there
которому легче всем прийти к доллару Да
is a very simple one. I have another question:
есть очень простым У меня другой вопрос
cars are bought in dollars; another
машины покупают в доллара другой
question does this bother you at all;
вопрос тебя это вообще
then they
волнует пото
praise Where everything is calculated, what
восхваляют Где у вас всё считается какая
difference does it make, here you are sitting like a little
разница вот ты сидишь так маленькая
girl, yes, in some kind of Yes, and you’re worried about
девушка да в каком-то Да и Переживаешь
what’s going on in Ukraine?  - in short, with the
что в Украине что-то там короче с
hryvnia there, well, it works,
гривной там что ну это работает ну типа
like a boomerang effect, do you care what’s
как эффект бумеранга вас волнует что
happening in our country? No, no,
происходит у нас в стране Нет не нет
look at us, we generally felt very bad
смотри нас нам вообще было очень плохо
that our people didn’t care about what was
что у нас людей не волновало что
happening in your country. So you  so
происходит у вас в стране Так вы так
you think, you answer,
думаете Вы отвечаете
they came to us now now, it’s not that
полезли к нам сейчас сейчас мы не то что
we care about what’s happening in your country,
нас волнует что делается у вас в стране
we directly influence the events in your
мы прямо влияем на события в вашем
country, someone is being blown up there, and somewhere
стране кого-то там взрывают да где-то
someone is under the field doing someone
кто-то под полье делает кто-то пустил
derailed  a train exploded somewhere
под откос поезд где-то взорвался
tanks exploded, yes, that is, now
взорвались цистерны да то есть сейчас
Ukraine has an absolutely serious influence on
Украина абсолютно серьёзно влияет на
Russia and we will do everything to ensure that the
Россию и мы будем делать всё чтобы это
Russian Federation falls apart and everything And you are
Российская Федерация распалась всё А вас
a shark,
акула
you have been trying to do this for more than a year now
вы пытаетесь это делать уже год с лишним
I don’t know how many times there  I was promised in the
Я не знаю сколько там раз мне обещали в
roulette chat we will come to you, we and de
чат рулетки мы к вам придём мы и де
parish come already to the Belgorod region
приход приходят уже в Белгородскую обла
with you Prim and the whole
при к вам Прим и всю
country I’m sitting on February 23
страну сижу я 23 февраля
on Lord And where is the region, tell me the
на Господи А где же есть область скажи
region at least Yes, what difference does it
область хотя бы Да какая разница у вас
make if you are there?  people from Belgorod were also
смо если ты вот люди из Белгорода тоже
making fun of them. Yes, they were making fun of them, making
прикалывались Да прикалывались
fun of them, and then something became not funny.
прикалывались а потом что-то не смешное
Tell me why you don’t like
стало А расскажи за что ты не любишь
Uzbeks. I don’t like men’s
узбеков Мне не нравится именно мужское
men’s  component of the Uzbeks because
мужская составляющая узбеков потому что
these are the people who have a wife can
это люди которые имею жену могут ко мне
come up to me on the street and say girl
на улице подойти и сказать девушка
Come with me so it’s only the Uzbeks who
Поехали со мной так это только узбеки
do that yes Well basically yes and the
делают так да Ну в основном да а
Tajiks are less Tajiks and the Chechens
таджики таджики меньше а чеченцы
Chen at least have the honor but how do you How do you
Чен хоть честь имеют а как вы Как вы
know what’s going on?  It was an Uzbek who told you this
узнаете что вот это вам сказал именно
because they have one
узбек потому что у них есть одна
wonderful distinctive feature: narrow
прекрасная отличительная черта так узкие
eyes. I understand
глаза Я понял то
that in this world only Uzbeks have
есть это в этом мире только у узбеков
narrow eyes; Kazakhs also Yes, but  Kazakhs
узкие глаза казахи ещё Да но казахи
are different, Kazakhs don’t
отличаются казахи не
speak, we’ve heard how you
разговаривают вот слышали как вот у вас
have a Ukrainian accent, people have an
есть украинский акцент у людей есть
Uzbek accent, a Kazar
узбекский акцент казарский
Belarusian accent, there are Americans when
белорусский акцент есть американцы когда
they speak Russian, the
разговаривают на русском языке слышно
dialect is heard is not the same. How, for example, how can you
диалект не тот А как например как
distinguish an Uzbek from a Kazakh by their accent? A
отличить вот по акценту узбека от
Kazakh has a
казаха у казаха
more understandable Russian language  That is, if
более понятный русский язык То есть если
you listen by ear, I
слушать на слух б я даже воспроизвести
wouldn’t even be able to reproduce it, but you need to listen to
не смогу но это нужно слушать
it. Well, an Uzbek will say a
зча Ну узбек скажет
Kazakh girl  will do, he’ll say Well, there’s a
девушка казах подойдёт скажет Ну там
little bit of cheating, but in terms of
чуть-чуть измен но в плане того
what the girl will say, it’s good, and the Tajik will
что девушка он скажет хорошо а таджик
say what the Tajik will say, maybe
скажет таджи скажет може быть тоже
the girl also doesn’t understand how
девушка усто не понял Как жи
narrow he is, an Uzbek, if the girl and eyes are not
узкий то узбек если девушка и глаза не
narrow, Tajik Well, not a Tajik, maybe a
узкие таджик Ну не таджик может быть
Dagestani, an Armenian  someone What a
дагестанец армянин ещё кто-то Какой
wide range of peoples yes Interesting yes
широкий спектр народов да Интересно да у
we have a lot of people of different nations Yeah
нас людей разных народов очень много Ага
got it Cool yes it turns out
понял Прикольно да оказывается
uh Tajik is a Dagestani so conditionally
ээ таджика дагестанца так условно
there is no such people from Dagestani  Dagestani
дагестанца нет такого народа дагестанец
Yes, there are a lot of ZhT Kumyks Laks Dargins And
Да там много ЖТ кумыки лакцы даргинцы И
so on So the Armenians are almost the same,
так дальше Вот и армяна почти одинаковые
I understand No, they are different They are different, but that’s
они я понял Нет они разные Они разные а
good And for example, the Russians pester the
хорошо А например а русские пристают
Russians, but a Russian has never
русские но ко мне ни разу русский не
pestered me at all And what is so sad about them
приставал на у А что у них так печально
like not  Like all the Uzbeks kicked out all the
типа не Типа все узбеки выгнали всех
Russians there. No, I understand. What do you
русских там Да нет понял А как ты
think Russia is for
считаешь Россия для
Russians? Yes, no, that is, Russia is not for
русских Да нет то есть Россия не для
Russians. No, well, anyone can come here.
русских Не ну сюда может приезжать
Russia is for  Russian yes or no For
любой Россия для русских да или нет Для
everyone, everyone can come, that is, Russia is
всех могут приехать все то есть Россия
not for Russians Well, for Russians, that
не для русских Ну для для русских то
is, Russia is, well, in fact, if
есть Россия - это ну типа по факту если
I was born in Russia, this is my country But they
я родилась в России это моя страна Но к
come to us and
нам приезжают
they say Russia is for Russians Yes, these are
го вот говорят Россия для русских Да вот
your nationalists  then Russia is for Russians
ваши националисты то Россия для русских
or for non-Russians for
или для нерусских для
everyone, that is, for non-Russians too, Russia
всех то есть для нерусских тоже Россия
yes Well, they can come here, not well, it’s not like
да Ну они могут сюда приехать не ну не
non-Russians live here What does it
то что у вас и живут нерусские Что
mean
значит
when it’s good Russia - Whose
при хорошо Россия - Это чья
country is this? Well, if we take it this way, Russia is,
страна Ну го если брать так Россия - это
well, Ours  country  ours - This is whose Well, Russians,
ну Наша страна наша - Это чья Ну россиян
that is, of all all peoples No, well, not
то есть всех всех народов Да не ну не
like I wouldn’t say that this is the person
типа я бы не сказала что вот человек
who came, I don’t know from
который приехал я не знаю с
Dagestan, like, well, damn it, well, according to the
Дагестана типа это ну блин ну по
documents, He lives in this country, this is
документам Он живёт в этой стране это
his country, But he was, like, originally born
его страна Но он типа изначально родился
in another country, that is, If a person
в другой стране то есть Если человек
was born in Dagestan and came to
родился в Дагестане так и приехал в
Russia, then in short he is not quite
Россию то значит короче он не совсем
Russian Yes, according to his documents he is a
россияне Да он по документам он
Russian fact of the matter, I
россиянин факт
won’t have any questions for him,
уга вопросов никаких к нему не будет у
my stepfather is Armenian No, go
меня отчим Армянин Не ну
figure  come on, a man who was born in
поди давай так человек который родился в
Dagestan Yes, and he came to Russia, so here
Дагестане Да и приехал в Россию так вот
he is Well, how does he differ from other
он Ну чем он отличается от других
Russians
россиян
then with his roots, what
тогда своими корнями что у него Ну то
are his Well, that is, And what are his roots? Well, roots, how is he
есть И что корни Ну корни чем он
different from us, what does he look
отличается от нас как он выглядит его
like?  to name this
корни его в принципе как назвать-то эту
tradition, he has other traditions, this is what makes
традиции у него другие традиции вот этим
him different from us from you, this is From whom From
он от нас отличается от вас это От кого
those Well, from the Slavs, let’s say He’s a
От тех Ну от славян допустим Он
Muslim, I guess Stop like that, and Russia -
мусульманин по поди Стоп так а Россия -
This is that there are no Slavs in the country. Why are you
Это что страна славян нет Да что ж ты
saying that he’s different from  Well,
говоришь что он и отличается от Ну а он
what is he  you want to say that if
что вы хотите сказать что если при
he is a Dagestani, he is no different from us.
дагестанец он от нас Ничем не отличается
Maybe it’s you who are different from him, look,
Может это вы от него отличаетесь смотри
Russia is the country of anyone who is
Россия - это страна кого
Russian at all, but after all, we
вообще русских о то всё-таки мы
dug up your Russia is a country of Russians,
раскопали твою Россия - это страна русс
but at the same time, people can live here
но при этом здесь могут жить люди любой
anywhere  you will read that Russia
нао где ты такое прочитаешь что Россия -
is a country of Russians, your Constitution
это страна русских у вас в Конституции
says that this is the country of your
сказано что это страна вашего
multinational
многонационального
people, a multinational country Yes, yes, it
народа многонациональная страна Да да
doesn’t say there, not a single
там там не сказано ни в одном вашем
document of yours says this is a country, but this is ra,
документе не сказано это страна а это ра
this is my concept, I don’t A  what is this,
это моё понятие я не А что это так
wait, is this the country of the Chechens or not? Well,
подожди а это страна чеченцев или нет Ну
if a Chechen was born here, then
если чеченец здесь родился то
yes, that is, if a Chechen was born in Chechnya,
да то есть если чеченец родился в Чечне
then Russia is his country or not, according to the
то Россия - это его страна или нет по
document, if then his country, if
документом если то его страна если у
he has his own
него есть своя
homeland, Chechnya is there, that is, initially
Родина Чечня там так то есть изначально
his country is
его страна - это
Chechnya; later he has, well,
Чечня в дальнейшем у него есть Ну ти
citizenship,
гражданство
he is already his country, both here and there. But
он уже как бы его страна и там и тут Но
initially, his country, if he was born in
изначально его страна если он родился в
Chechnya, is, well, his country there. If I were
Чечне это ну страна его там Если бы я
born in
родилась в
Kazakhstan  initially it would have been my
Казахстане изначально была бы моей
home country Well, like
родной страной Ну типа
Kazakhstan, it turns out, look, that
Казахстан получается смотри то
is, people who were born in Buryatia,
есть люди которые родились в Бурятии
who were born in Chechnya, who
которые родились в Чечне которые
were born in Yakutia like that. They have no right
родились В Якутии так Они не имеют права
to Russia since you are Slavs. No, they
на Россию так как вы славяне Да нет
have rights. I say that the person was born
имеют пра я и говорю что человек родился
here and was born  there are two different things
здесь и родился там это две разные вещи
If a person was born in another country,
Если человек родился в другой стране
initially his native country in which
изначально его Страна родная в которой
he was born lived there for some time, he
он родился какое-то время прожил там он
came
приехал
here so that I understand, for example, you were born
сюда чтобы я понял например ты родилась
in Moscow
в Москве
[music]
[музыка]
and another guy  was born in Chechnya in
да другой мужик родился в Чечне в
Grozny and the third was born in Buryatia in
Грозном и третий родился в Бурятии в
Ulan
Улан
ud whose country is of these three which
уд чья страна вот из этих трёх какая у
country is theirs Who was born in their
них страна у кого Кто родился вная
native one Well, if I was born in Moscow my
Родная ну если я родилась в Москве моя
native country is Russia if I am there a
родная страна - это Россия если я там
person was born in Chechnya his native  the
человек родился в Чечне его родная
country is
страна
Chechnya, if he came here, then his second
Чечня если он приехал сюда то его второй
country in which he lives will
страной в которой он проживает будет
be Russia, but some who
являться Россия но некоторые которые
come here for a while purely to
сюда Приезжают на некоторое время чисто
earn extra money there,
там подзаработать онино
that is, it turns out that if a person was born
То есть получается Если человек родился
in Moscow, then his country is Russia  If a
в Москве то его страна Россия Если
person was born in Grozny, then his country is
человек родился в Грозном то его страна
Chechnya If a person was born in Ulan ud, his
Чечня Если человек родился в Улан уд его
country is Buryatia Yes,
страна Бурятия Да свидетельство о
when is the birth certificate issued by which country?
рождения когда выдаётся какой страной
If a person was born in Chechnya What kind of
Если человек родился в Чечне Какое у
birth certificate does he have? Which one
него свидетельство о рождении Какое
Please tell me. In Russia,
Расскажите мне пожалуйста У нас в России
our birth certificate is issued.  the
выдаётся наше свидетельство о рождении
Russian Federation is written there,
там прописано Российская Федерация там
according to all the documents, and in Chechnya in Chechnya the
по всем докумен а в Чечне в Чечне
Chechen Republic Yes, Ikea is there Well,
Чеченская республика Да Икея там Ну у
they have their own documents Yeah, I understand Chech okay
них свои документы Ага понял чеч окей
okay  Let's take Kazakhstan, approximately, they have
хорошо возьмём Казахстан примерно у них
their own I understood Yes, I understood, it just turns out
сво я понял Да я понял просто получается
that in Moscow you in Russia
да что то есть в Москве у вас в России
issue your own birth certificate where it
выдаются свои свидетельство рождения где
says Russian Federation If
пишется Российская Федерация Если
a person was born in Buryatia, his
человек родился в Бурятии у него
birth certificate says Buryatia,
свидетельство рождения написано Бурятия
if he was born in Dagestan, he has
если он родился в Дагестане у него
a certificate  birth in Dagestan,
свидетельство рождения на Дагестан да
yes it turns out Well, how does it work? Like in
получается Ну а как это работает типа в
Kazakhstan they write that a
Казахстане пишут что свидетельство о
birth certificate is like the Russian Federation, what kind
рождении типа Российской Федерации что
of nonsense is this? You have people in Ukraine when
это за бред У вас люди в Украине когда
a child is
ребёнок
born. And what will happen if a person is there?
тся А что будет если человеку там вот
for example, he will pay a bribe, he will be born in
например занесёт взятку он он родится в
Dagestan, for example, or in Buryatia Yes, but
Дагестане например или в Бурятии Да а
they will write down that his place of birth is the
ему запишут что место рождения
Russian Federation What do you think? Well, it’s
Российская Федерация Как ты считаешь Ну
possible. If he comes here and makes a
можно Если он приедет сюда и сделает
birth certificate here, well, sort of
свидетельство о рождении здесь ну типа
in fact. Well, if he was just born, he was
по факту Ну если он только родился его
immediately transported, but he  was born there but
сразу перевезли но он родился там но
initially here, well, he himself was there, a
изначально здесь вот ну самого дест там
month later he was brought to Russia, he had
через месяц его привезли в Россию он
never lived there in his life, like in
никогда в жизни там не жил типа вот в
another country. Well, he’s here, he’s like in
другой стране Ну он здесь он типа в
Russia, he’s a Russian, another country, then.
России он россиянин друго страна то То
yes it turns out If a person from Buryatia
есть получается Если человек из Бурятии
or from Chechnya or from Adygea comes to
или из Чечни или из там Адыгеи приедет в
Russia Yes he can become a Russian
Россию Да он смо может стать россиянином
Well of course the documents
Ну конечно документы
are processed Yes it’s cool Yes And by the way who are you
оформляются Да прикольно Да А ты кем
working as a streamer job
работаешь стримером работа
Well you said that you go to work there
Ну ты говорила что там идёшь на работу
or who you work for Well that’s me  then
или кем работаешь Ну это я тогда
I was working now I’m already there now well
работала сейчас я уже там сейчас ну
really Streamer really Streamer Yes it
реально Стример реально Стример Да не
can’t Streamer must have some kind of
может Стример должен каким-то
intelligence
интеллектом
I’m like when I come here to
обладать я типа когда я захожу сюда с
talk about politics  about
целью пообщаться насчёт политики насчёт
politics, I initially Damn it’s a pity that I
политики я изначально Блин жалко
switched
переключил
that to my Telegram right now the VN
та на мий Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
axis apok tse more and more important YouTube taking
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the ORV srg to your ban and even
нас через срг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
more videos I don’t show people often don’t
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about the stream That’s
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
why we need Mali operational  link to
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
write directly at once and while there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okrim video sche tezh  tsikava korisna
окрим видео ще теж цикава корисна
information and we are guilty of you trimati
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
postiyny operative link
постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini write
YouTube Слава украини пиши